

Hoang Bao Vo (Andy)

Date of birth: 19/09/1998 | **Place of birth:** Binh Dinh, Vietnam | **Nationality:** Vietnamese |

Sex: Male | Phone: (+84) 989546292 (Mobile) | Email: andy.vo.webdeveloper@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bao-vo-hoang | Github: https://github.com/andyvo190998 | Portfolio:

https://andyvo190998.github.io/animated-portfolio/

Address: 36 Bờ Bao Tân Thắng, 7600, Hồ Chí Minh, Vietnam (Home)

ABOUT MYSELF

With more than 4 years of experience working in startup environment with NextJS, ReactJS, Typescript, NodeJS, Python, REST-APIs, databases such as Postgres, Redis, MongoDB, MySQL, and experienced with Microservices Architecture. I am confident to handle most of the tasks related to web applications. I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, hard-working person who can be able to adapt to all challenging situations. I can work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. Please visit my GitHub repositories and portfolio website to see my work to learn more about me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOLARBK - HO CHI MINH, VIETNAM

SOLAR ENERGY ENGINEER - 10/12/2019 - 31/12/2020

Research and find out new technologies that improve the efficiency of solar modules, receive feedback from clients and find the solution to fix that issue on Solar panels.

FULLERTON HEALTH - SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE

WEB DEVELOPERS - 01/07/2021 - 01/10/2021

- Developed, maintained, and enhanced website features using **ReactJS** and **NodeJS**, ensuring responsive and efficient user interactions. Debugged and resolved frontend and backend issues to maintain optimal functionality and seamless user experience. Collaborated with cross-functional team members to implement new features and continuously improve website performance.
- Tech Stack: ReactJS, NodeJS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Ⅲ KIUTRA GMBH – MUNICH, GERMANY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - 01/04/2022 - 11/2024

- Developed responsive front-end applications using ReactJS, focusing on delivering seamless user experiences.
 Designed and implemented scalable REST and WebSocket APIs using Flask and Quart for efficient backend
 communication. Built event-driven microservices and maintained Python-based middleware to support
 inter-process messaging. Supported the hardware team by integrating software solutions and setting up
 systems for smooth software-hardware interoperability.
- **Tech Stack:** ReactJS, NodeJS (NestJS), Flask, Quart, WebSocket, REST APIs, Python, Microservices, Event-Driven Architecture, Middleware, Software-Hardware Integration

III JOCHEN SCHWEIZER MYDAYS GROUP − MÜNCHEN, GERMANY

FULLSTACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - 01/12/2024 - CURRENT

• Design and build scalable, cloud-native web applications with a focus on clean architecture and high maintainability. Develop intuitive, performant UIs using **React** and **TypeScript**, and implement robust backend services with **NestJS**, **PHP**, and **REST APIs**. Apply **Hexagonal Architecture** and **Domain-Driven Design (DDD)** to ensure modular, testable codebases. Drive quality through extensive **unit** and **end-to-end testing**, including in-

house tooling. Deploy microservices via **Docker** and **Kubernetes**, with CI/CD workflows. Collaborate across teams to deliver high-impact software that meets performance, reliability, and scalability goals.

• **Tech Stack:** React, TypeScript, NestJS, PHP, REST APIs, Docker, Kubernetes, PostgreSQL, Redis, Jest, E2E testing, Hexagonal Architecture, DDD

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/06/2016 - 01/10/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Ho Chi Minh University Technology and Education

My major is material technology, more specifically, I study about some devices like Transistors, MOSFET, LED, Sensors, TCO,... nanostructure, simulation properties of materials, semiconductors, thin film technology,... deep knowledge of semiconductors and Transistor and General Electronics

Address 1 Vo Van Ngan, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam, 71300, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | Website hcmute.edu.vn |

Field of study Physics, Chemistry, Physical sciences not elsewhere classified | Final grade GPA: 7.64/10 | Thesis Thesis: 9.6/10

01/04/2021 - 01/12/2023 Augsburg, Germany

MASTER OF SCIENCE University of Augsburg

Continues with the subjects of bachelor's degree, I keep digging deeper into Semiconductor Technology, and gain more knowledge of Semiconductor devices (E.g Transistor, Solar cells,...), understand the way it works and how to create it. Beside of that, I am learning the properties of other materials such as Metals, and polymer composites,...

Address Universitätsstraße 2, Augsburg, 86159, Augsburg, Germany | Website www.uni-augsburg.de |

Field of study Chemistry, Physics | **Thesis** The properties of Cul thin films prepared by spin coating.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **VIETNAMESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user

SKILLS

React, Next.js, React Native | typescrypt | Python | NodeJS | Angular TS, Angular JS | Microservices Infrastructure | PHP | DevOps

HONOURS AND AWARDS

28/12/2021

Web developer - Freecodecamp

From this course, i was learning a lot of basic knowledges about javascript and data structure.

Link https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc71b5460b-8133-41f4-94fc-5727c76f5015/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

26/02/2022

web developer - Udemy

This course guides me from front end to back end and including data base like MongoDB.

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-acdd3aa5-ddc5-4778-93b5-c2c5eee59f29.pdf